optokingdom.com 2019-07-03

# Privacy Policy /LED Outdoor Screen Website

Thank you for accessing our website. We respect your privacy and take your online information security very seriously. In order to make convenient and efficient online shopping system and provide best product, efficient service to every user, we will collect and record a variety of information when you visit our website.

This Privacy Policy explains why your information will be collected and how we collect, use, and (under certain conditions) disclose your personal information. This Privacy Policy also explains the steps we have taken to secure your personal information. Finally, this Privacy Policy explains your options regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information. By visiting our Site, you accept the practices described in this Notice.

**The reason of we collect your personal information and what kind of information will be collected.**  
Optokingdom believe it is very important for you to know what personal information we collect. When you visit our website your computer's IP address might be collected. We will collect such your name, your name, your address, your telephone number, your email address, and your credit card number when your register your account on our website. This information related with you directly and some other information that you may not consider as your privacy, we might be collect. Such as your language preferences, how many times you've visited the site, and which page you've clicked on etc.

**Personal information use and why**  
**1.** As do most catalog and Internet wholesalers, we sometimes use others to perform specific functions on our behalf. When we disclose information to these service providers, we disclose information to help them to perform their service. When you purchase goods from our website your address and phone number will be collected. In order send the goods fast and safe to you. We will share your name, your phone number and your address to express company.

**2.** We use your personal information to process your order and provide you with customer service. We may internally use your personal information to improve our Site's content and layout, to improve our outreach and for our own marketing efforts (including marketing our services and products to you), and to determine general marketplace information about visitors to this Site.

**3.** In order to provide your best customer service we will share your information for internal use. This is measure is convenient for us to send an email to you to solve your problem and communicate with you efficiency.

**4.** When your place your order and pay for it. To help you buy products and provide customer service to you, we must provide your credit card number to financial-services corporations such as credit-card processors and issuers. When we submit your credit card number for authorization, we use state-of-the-art data encryption to protect your information.

**5.** We may be required to disclose such information in response to requests from law-enforcement officials conducting investigations, subpoenas, a court order, or if we are otherwise required to disclose such information by law. We also will release personal information where disclosure is necessary to protect our legal rights, enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect ourselves or others. For example, we may share information to reduce the risk of fraud or if someone uses or attempts to use our Site for illegal reasons or to commit fraud .We may be required to disclose such information in response to requests from law-enforcement officials conducting investigations, subpoenas, a court order, or if we are otherwise required to disclose such information by law. We also will release personal information where disclosure is necessary to protect our legal rights, enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect ourselves or others. For example, we may share information to reduce the risk of fraud or if someone uses or attempts to use our Site for illegal reasons or to commit fraud.

**Your rights to operate your information**  
You can use your account to make a review on our website. And you can change your personal information freely. If you don't want to use your account you can cancel or delete your account and your personal information.

**NOTICE**  
We do not sell, trade, license, or otherwise disclose your specific personal information or financial information to anyone except the content we mention on this privacy policy. Do not operate your account to violate the law!  

**Updates This Policy**

We have taken a number of measures to ensure that when you visit our website is secure, so your privacy is always respected, this Privacy Policy if there are any changes or updates, we will from time to time to remind you to view our privacy policy. If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy, please contact us.
